Data Quality Platforms Melissa's Full Spectrum DQ Approach. [Learn More](https://www.melissa.com/data-quality "Learn More about Melissa Data Quality Solutions")
    
    * * *
    
    [Unison
    
    Validate, Cleanse & Maintain Data Quality Without Programming.](https://www.melissa.com/customer-data-validation-platform)
    
    [
    
    GovCloud Address Suite
    
    Verify global addresses & access change-of-address records for the U.S.](https://www.melissa.com/govcloud-address-suite)
    
    ETL/MDM PlatformsMelissa offers a host of solutions for full spectrum data quality to ensure the success of your data.

    Data Verification Tools Melissa’s Smart, Sharp Tool Approach. [Learn More](https://www.melissa.com/data-quality "Learn More about Melissa Data Quality Solutions")
    
    * * *
    
    [Address Verification
    
    Clean your addresses to improve mail & fulfillment.](https://www.melissa.com/address-verification)
    
    [Phone Verification
    
    Ensure mobile & landlines are accurate & callable.](https://www.melissa.com/phone-verification)
    
    [Email Verification
    
    Validate emails before hitting send.](https://www.melissa.com/email-verification)
    
    [Name Verification
    
    Parse & standardize first & last names for personalization.](https://www.melissa.com/name-verification)
    
    [Matching / Dedupe
    
    Combine multiple records into one golden record.](https://www.melissa.com/data-deduplication)
    
    [Customer Data Management
    
    Discover best-in-class data quality in one platform.](https://www.melissa.com/customer-data-validation-platform)
    
    [Profiling
    
    Analyze your data to improve its quality over time.](https://www.melissa.com/data-profiling)
    
    [Generalized Cleansing
    
    Cleanse any type of data fast & easy.](https://www.melissa.com/data-cleansing)
    
    [Batch Address Cleansing
    
    Clean addresses in batch to improve delivery & customer satisfaction.](https://www.melissa.com/batch-address-cleansing)
    
    Popular Products
    
    * * *

    Identity Verification Increase compliance, reduce fraud and improve onboarding. [Visit the Melissa Identity Suite](https://www.melissa.com/identity-verification)
    
    * * *
    
    [Personator Identity
    
    Global eIDV tools for KYC/KYB Checks and AML compliance.](https://www.melissa.com/personator-identity)
    
    [Personator Consumer
    
    Fraud protection and contact verification for U.S. and Canada only.](https://www.melissa.com/personator-consumer)
    
    [Melissa ID Scan
    
    Mobile app to verify ID docs and biometrics.](https://www.melissa.com/id-document-verification)
    
    KYC + KYB Capabilities
    
    * * *

    E-commerce/CRM Apps and APIs for higher conversions, better data and more reliable shipping. [See All Melissa Integrations](https://www.melissa.com/integrations "Learn More about Melissa Integrations")
    
    * * *
    
    [Address Autocomplete
    
    Capture verified addresses on forms quickly with autocomplete technology.](https://www.melissa.com/address-autocomplete "Learn More about Melissa Address Autocomplete Solutions")
    
    [IP Location
    
    Validate IP & append geolocation data.](https://www.melissa.com/ip-location)
    
    [Street Route
    
    Find distance & travel time by lat/long pairs.](https://www.melissa.com/geocoding)
    
    * * *
    
    E-commerce AppsMelissa Address Validation for Shopify, Stripe & Shopware

    CRM AppsMelissa Address Validation for Dynamics 365 and Salesforce

    Enrich Gain insight into who and where your customers are.
    
    * * *
    
    [Geocoding / Reverse Geocoding
    
    Convert street addresses to lat/long pairs.](https://www.melissa.com/geocoding)
    
    [U.S. Property Verify & Append
    
    Add 400 fields of property & mortgage data.](https://www.melissa.com/property-data)
    
    [Consumer Verify & Append
    
    Access data on 2.1 billion consumer records.](https://www.melissa.com/demographic-data)
    
    [Business Verify & Append
    
    Get firmographic data based on company name & address.](https://www.melissa.com/firmographic-data)
    
    [Property Hazard Risk
    
    Identify Risk for Water, Air, Earth & Fire Hazard for U.S Properties.](https://www.melissa.com/property-hazard-risk)
    
    [Contact Record Completion
    
    Add missing names, phone numbers, email addresses, postal addresses.](https://www.melissa.com/contact-record-completion)
    
    Popular Products
    
    * * *

    Mailing Qualify for postal discounts with USPS CASS & PAVE Certified solutions.
    
    * * *
    
    [Postal Presorting
    
    Group mail by ZIP for postage discounts.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/direct-mail/presort-object)
    
    [NCOA Change of Address
    
    Update the addresses of U.S. & Canadian customers that have moved.](https://www.melissa.com/ncoalink-processing)
    
    Popular Products
    
    * * *

    Industries See how Melissa's solutions work across industries.
    
    * * *
    
    [Healthcare
    
    Better Data for Better Patient Care and Increased Revenue.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/healthcare)
    
    [CRM
    
    Improve CRM Data to Enhance the Customer Experience.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/crm-call-centers)
    
    [Insurance
    
    Improve Customer, Property & Risk Intelligence.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/insurance)
    
    [Ecommerce
    
    Create a Better Customer Experience and Reduce Cart Abandonment.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/ecommerce)
    
    [Mailing & Shipping
    
    Improve Deliverability, Response, and Save on Costs.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/mailing-shipping)
    
    [Real Estate
    
    Improve Property Intelligence to Close the Deal.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/real-estate)
    
    [Fintech & Financial Services
    
    Achieve KYC Compliance and Reduce the Risk of Fraud.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/banking)
    
    [Transportation & Logistics
    
    Increase Accuracy in Spatial Analysis, Mapping, and Location Intelligence.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/gis)
    
    [GOVT & Public Sector
    
    Maintain Communication with Constituents & Cut Waste.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/government-public-sector)
    
    [Online Gaming & Casinos
    
    Prevent Fraud, Maintain Compliance & Improve Profitability.](https://www.melissa.com/industries/online-gaming-and-casinos)

    Data Hygiene Keep your mailing list up-to-date, qualify for postal discounts & reduce UAA mail.
    
    * * *
    
    [Address Verification / CASS ® & DPV ®
    
    Correct addresses to improve mail piece deliverability.](https://www.melissa.com/address-verification)
    
    [DSF 2®
    
    Save on postage with premium address verification.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/direct-mail/dsf2)
    
    [NCOALink ®
    
    Find the addresses of U.S. customers that have moved.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/direct-mail/ncoa-link)
    
    [Canadian NCOA & Address Verification
    
    Update addresses for moving Canadian customers.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/direct-mail/canada-ncoa)
    
    [MCOA & PCOA Change of Address
    
    Capture new moved to addresses not recorded by USPS.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/direct-mail/mcoa-pcoa)
    
    [International Address Validation
    
    Clean & correct street addresses around the world.](https://www.melissa.com/global-bureau-services)
    
    [Email Verification
    
    Validate your email addresses to improve email marketing.](https://www.melissa.com/email-verification)
    
    [Dedupe
    
    Eliminate duplicate records from your mailing list to reduce costs.](https://www.melissa.com/data-deduplication)
    
    [Suppression
    
    Remove undesirable records who shouldn't receive your mail.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/direct-mail/deceased-suppression)
    
    Data Enhancement Enrich your consumer or business records for greater insight & omni-channel marketing success.
    
    * * *
    
    [Consumer Demographics
    
    Learn more about who your customers are.](https://www.melissa.com/consumer-demographic-reference-data-sets)
    
    [Business Firmographics
    
    Improve lead scoring with detailed company info.](https://www.melissa.com/firmographic-data)
    
    [Premium Phone Append
    
    Add consumer or business mobile/landline numbers.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/data-append/phone-append)
    
    [Reverse Phone Append
    
    Find mailing addresses with a phone number.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/data-append/reverse-phone-append)
    
    [Premium Email Append
    
    Add consumer or business email addresses to postal lists.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/data-append/email-append)
    
    [Reverse Email Append
    
    Find mailing address with an email address.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/data-append/reverse-email-append)
    
    [Geocoding
    
    Add precise location data to your list.](https://www.melissa.com/geocoding)
    
    [Property Append
    
    Add property & mortgage data for better analysis.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/data-append/property-data-append)
    
    [SIC / NAICS Coding
    
    Identify companies by business type.](https://www.melissa.com/direct/data-append/naics-sic-code-service)
    
    SaaS Clean and update your data in the cloud, no software to maintain.
    
    * * *
    
    [Listware
    
    Data cleansing in Excel or Online.](https://www.melissa.com/saas/)
    
    [Mailers Online
    
    Cloud postal processing for USPS/Canada Post mail.](https://www.melissa.com/service/presort/uploadws.aspx)

    * [About Melissa
        
        Global leaders in contact data quality.](https://www.melissa.com/company/about)
    * [Partners
        
        Melissa's technology & solutions partners.](https://www.melissa.com/company/partners#be-a-partner)
    * [Customers
        
        View our over 10,000 satisfied customers.](https://www.melissa.com/company/customers)
    * [Resources
        
        Download Catalogs, Whitepapers & more.](https://www.melissa.com/resources/#language=english)
    * [Events
        
        Register for our events and webinars.](https://www.melissa.com/company/events)
    
    * [Blogs
        
        Melissa data quality & direct mail news.](https://www.melissa.com/resources/communities)
    * [Videos
        
        Video library - watch on demand.](https://www.melissa.com/videos/)
    * [E-Commerce Calculator
        
        How much is bad data costing you?](https://www.melissa.com/calculators/ecommerce)
    * [Address Experts
        
        Articles, definitions & address solutions.](https://www.melissa.com/address-experts/)
    * [Privacy Center
        
        Privacy policy, data collection & more.](https://www.melissa.com/privacy)

Our Solutions

Data Quality Platforms

* * *

Data Verification Tools

* * *

Identity Verification

* * *

E-Commerce / CRM

* * *

Enrich

* * *

Mailing

* * *

Industries

* * *

Our Services

Data Hygiene

* * *

Data Enhancement

* * *

SaaS

* * *

Our Data

Our Data

* * *

Pricing

Pricing

* * *

More

More

* * *

Explore Melissa

Explore Melissa

* * *

1. [](https://www.melissa.com/ "Melissa")
2. Privacy

Melissa Privacy Center
======================

Melissa Data Corporation (“Melissa”) considers itself a steward of the information it collects, maintains, and utilizes. Our responsibility is to ensure the security of the information in our care and to maintain the privacy of consumers through appropriate, responsible use. As a licensed data broker, Melissa maintains a comprehensive information security program of administrative, technical and physical safeguard measures, which are independently verified through third-party audits to verify process security, availability, and confidentiality. The links below provide a comprehensive overview of how we obtain and use the information we receive, along with an explanation of your rights as a consumer to manage and protect your personal information.

[Privacy Policy
--------------

Privacy Policy explains how Melissa collects, uses, & discloses personal information.

Read Privacy Policy](https://www.melissa.com/privacy-policy "Read Melissa's Privacy Policy")

[Privacy Notice for Residents of California
------------------------------------------

The California Consumer Protection Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) for residents of the state of California.

Read Privacy Notice for Residents of California](https://www.melissa.com/california-privacy-notice "Read Privacy Notice for Residents of California")

[State Law Privacy Notice
------------------------

Consumer privacy notice for residents of states with data privacy laws in place.

Read State Law Privacy Notice](https://www.melissa.com/state-law-privacy-notice "Read State Law Privacy Notice")

[Cookie Policy
-------------

How we use cookies to enhance user experience, analyze traffic, & personalize content.

Read Cookie Policy](https://www.melissa.com/cookie-policy "Read Cookie Policy")

[EU-US Data Privacy Framework
----------------------------

EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (“DPF Principles”) and our compliance.

Read EU-US Data Privacy Framework](https://www.melissa.com/eu-us-data-privacy-framework "Read EU-US Data Privacy Framework")

[Certifications & Compliance
---------------------------

Melissa undergoes security audits for data security, privacy, and compliance requirements.

View Certifications & Compliance](https://www.melissa.com/company/certifications "View Certifications & Compliance")

[Terms of Use
------------

Terms of use for visitors using our websites.

Read Terms of Use](https://www.melissa.com/terms "Read Terms of Use")

[](https://www.melissa.com/terms "Read Terms of Use")[Data Broker Registrations
-------------------------

Melissa complies with all state data broker registration requirements.

View Data Broker Registrations](https://www.melissa.com/data-broker-registrations "View Data Broker Registrations")

[](https://www.melissa.com/data-broker-registrations "View Data Broker Registrations")[Modern Slavery Statement
------------------------

Melissa recognizes it has a key role to play in preventing all types of modern slavery.

Read Modern Slavery Statement](https://www.melissa.com/modern-slavery-statement "Read Modern Slavery Statement")

Brands

Privacy

* * *

© Copyright 2024 by Melissa Data Corporation. All Rights Reserved.
